INTERSPECIES EXCHANGE
MADARA-GUMI
[screams, groans]
- [groans]
- [Melon chuckles]
The thing is,
I can't stand those spots of yours...
- [explosion]
- [grunts]
The Doku-Gumi wanna play.
[Savon] You fought well, boy.
Color me "impressed".
On behalf of the Doku-Gumi...
it wasn't our intention
to put you six feet under.
I have to say,
we aren't exactly "fan favorites"
around these parts.
And I'm getting tired of that.
So now, it's out with the discrimination
and in with the triumph.
Everyone's gonna see how special we are.
You're supposed to respect the Doku-Gumi...
- [rocks rumble]
- [sighs]
[Legoshi groans softly]
[Legoshi strains]
[panting]
[Legoshi] "A freshly severed limb
still has some life", right?
I'd feel sorry for it
if I let it get injured...
You're tellin' me
you took that blast...
just to protect that piece of tail?
I kinda panicked
and shoved it in my underwear,
I hope you don't take any offense.
A tail that's been cut off
can't be reattached.
The pride of the Doku-Gumi...
I entrust it to you.
[sighs]
[Ten] Yoo hoo!
[gasps]
You're pretty good for a little wolf cub.
[groans] Oh, don't tell me.
Now I have to fight a girl?
[Ten] All a woman has to do is touch you
and look at how your tail
stands straight up.
[gasps] Men really are
the simplest creatures, huh?
Any elegance you see in the Black Market
is going to be because of the Inari-Gumi.
Kind of like the charming seductress
your little tail can't seem to resist!
[Ten laughing]
[indistinct conversation]
[scoffs]
FESTIVAL SCHEDULE
3. SURPRISE ANNOUNCEMENT (FOOD)
[Mayor] This meat was artificially created
through the wonders of science.
Meaning, no one died
for this meat to exist.
And it can be consumed ethically.
The lab results show,
the cultured meat wasn't fully lab-grown,
it was partly made from fetal embryos.
The mayor, he investigated
the relationship
between you and your father,
and it seems he has some kind of evidence.
[sighs] It'll be fine.
I can do this.
[both grunting]
[both grunting, groaning]
- [Ten groans]
- [Legoshi exclaims in pain]
You going easy on me because I'm a girl?
If that's why you lose then that's on you.
Just remember, it wasn't me
who told you to do that.
Y'know, everyone always says,
female foxes are wicked creatures
who trick people
using their seductive charm.
I'm over that stereotype.
I want to win, grow stronger,
and prove them all wrong.
That's my sole focus.
[Legoshi] Yeah I get it.
Same for wolves.
No one really seems to understand us.
[sighs]
You see it in books and movies
all the time:
the wolf is the bad guy.
And it follows me around everywhere.
So I get it.
Is that right?
You're bold and insightful...
Still, doesn't mean you get mercy!
- [Ten groans]
- [Legoshi groans]
[yelps]
[panting]
It felt like you two
were taking your sweet time...
Apologies for giving into my impatience...
ONLY COMPANY RESEARCHERS BEYOND THIS POINT
I don't even know why I'm doing this.
[sighs]
Here it is.
Is that a live stream?
[Miguno] Yeah.
Check it out.
It's from the Black Market.
[Durham] The Black Market?
They're not allowed to show that.
Ough, he's covered in blood!
[exclaims in surprise] Is that...
It's Legoshi!
- [Durham] No way!
- [Miguno] That's crazy!
[crowd cheering]
[Mayor] The Zoolympics!
A world class competition involving...
some of the most talented
and skilled athletes on the planet.
Regardless of species,
of age, or of gender,
this event inspires all of us,
to strive for co-existence and prosperity.
However, before we can host the games,
our city needs to overcome some challenges
such as...
infrastructure,
devouring incidents
and construction delays.
In light of that,
we do have a major announcement
to share with you all!
Here it is.
- [male 1] Can they talk about that?
- [male 2] They finally admit it exists?
- [male 3] Oh, you know this is bad.
- [indistinct chatter]
NEW STADIUM BUILDING
[Louis] "Demolition of the Black Market"?
This isn't in the script!
[sighs] They set me up!
[Mayor] Quiet please!
Just settle down!
I know the Black Market is controversial.
Some say it's a necessity.
It acts as a safe haven for carnivores.
So they can satisfy their desire for meat.
Unfortunately, the Black Market
represents something much darker.
It's currently sheltering
a dangerous criminal.
Our sources tell us the gray wolf Legoshi,
is hiding out in the Market
[groans]
- So they found him?
- Well, it's about time.
Oh, Legoshi...
But fear not. We'll bring you news
of his arrest very soon.
- [crowd cheering]
- Right, my friend?
Right.
[applause]
[drums beating]
[tribal music playing]
[Melon grunting]
A beautiful red flower!
The first of many
that will bloom in my fields!
You can plant your flowers,
and they may bloom...
But it's pointless
if they don't bear fruit!
[both grunting]
[laughs maniacally]]
Finally!
Now you're getting it!
That's what I want to see!
[both grunting]
- [grunts]
- [groans]
[groaning in pain]
[Melon] Not trying to run away, are you?
[grunts]
When people run, I can't help but chase!
You can thank my leopard mom
for my hunting instincts.
[Legoshi] I won't be able to hold him off.
Melon will keep getting stronger,
and I'll run out of steam.
[grunts]
You've gotta tell me
how it feels to be the prey for once...
[thuds, straining]
I'm guessing that's a terror
you've never felt...
[gurgling]
[gasping]
[Legoshi] My dark self was always there
inside of me.
With his hands...
he could take any life he wanted...
All the worries I had about
my relationships with herbivores...
But those worries were so insignificant,
compared to the fear
felt by those who might be preyed upon.
I am...
I...
am...
[wolf howls]
[dogs howling]
[howling intensifies]
[all howl]
[Legoshi] It's them.
- Huh?
- [thud]
[howling]
- That's gotta be Legoshi!
- [giggles]
[all howling]
- [thud]
- [Legoshi groans]
[Melon growls]
[grunting]
[Louis] Legoshi,
you're really giving it your all.
Your pain and suffering though...
It's not less painful
just because you share it.
I know what I must do...
if both of us carry
our share of the burden
our strength will grow...
[Melon growls, chuckles]
[drums beating]
[both grunting]
- [Legoshi sighs in pain]
- [Melon grunts]
[Melon woos, chuckles]
[Melon] Admit it,
you're having a great time.
The mess. The gore. The pain...
makes you feel alive, doesn't it?
[laugh]
Ever notice,
hatred works both ways.
It's mutually beneficial.
When I show you my hatred,
you return that hate back to me.
Giving both of us
that precious will to live.
Exposing new parts of us,
parts that were just wasting away...
But it all wakes up as you and I
try to rip each other's throats out.
- [Legoshi grunts]
- [Melon chuckles]
There's nothing "lukewarm"
about this romance.
What we're experiencing right now
is true love!
[Legoshi screaming]
[Melon gasping]
[Melon chuckles, pants]
[chuckles]
I'm so getting fired for this.
[gasping]
[Legoshi] Melon?
Nice...
The experiment is working
just as I predicted.
We're witnessing the weakness of a hybrid.
He's reacting to the scent created
when carnivore and herbivore blood mixes.
Judging from this, it's quite effective.
[groans] I shouldn't have let you live.
[footsteps approaching]
This isn't a fight to the death.
It's supposed to be a turf war.
- And it's over.
- [Melon grunts]
[Melon grunts]
So what's next?
We all get cleaned up
and we're best friends? [laughs]
You've got to be kidding me
with this nonsense.
I know,
why don't we have
a little picnic together?
Foxes, tigers, and lizards,
all one happy family!
We should hold hands.
We'll just stop fighting
and leave the past in the past.
[laughing]
Now, let's raise a toast to our unity!
You're nothing but a bunch of fakes.
[Legoshi] I feel for you.
You're lonely.
Every interaction you've ever had
has been terrible for you.
But actually you're not alone.
I know exactly how you feel.
All of us,
searching for the right words
at the right time.
We become absorbed in these conversations.
If we learned to express ourselves...
- well then, someday--
- Just spare me the performance.
I'm not the audience for your speech.
[all gasp]
Let me go ahead and write the ending.
When you think about
the great masterpieces,
they always tend to end up in tragedy.
[laughs]
And this one's going to leave
a bad taste in your mouth...
Imagine a mixed beast dying
in a place like this!
- [all gasp]
- No!
[gunshot]
Oh, no... Melon, why?
[groans]
You should be more concerned about
someone else's life. [gasps for air]
She's at
the Festival of the Meteor, right?
- [female] Good work, Legoshi!
- [gasps softly]
Oh, the despair I've prepared for you...
I hope you savor every bit of it.
Legoshi...
Festival of the Meteor...
He talkin' about the Melda?
[Deshico] If it gets used at the venue...
[Haru] Let's go to the Festival Of
The Meteor, and light a candle together.
Make a promise.
Oh, no!
Excuse me! Sorry!
[male] Who won?
Haru...
[panting]
C'mon, grandson! Get on!
Grandpa!
[bike revving]
- [female] What is he saying?
- [male] You can't do that!
Louis, is your leg bothering you?
Oh, no.
- It's not a problem.
- Well, then, keep going...
[Louis] Earlier today, we announced
the demolition of the Black Market.
I ask,
to every carnivore that is here tonight.
Is that something you're all okay with?
Uh...
I see your fangs are yellow.
I'm guessing
you love eating horse meat, right?
I see you sweat a lot.
You probably eat a lot of oily organ meat.
Why is he going off script?!
I ask you.
Can we really blame them for their nature?
Sometimes we laugh together,
and sometimes we cry.
But when we see the fangs in their mouths,
we can't help but have a reaction.
The truth is
carnivores are going to eat meat.
That's just a simple fact of life.
[male 4] This is making me uncomfortable.
[Louis] Herbivores and carnivores
should interact.
That's the only way forward.
[female reporter] This has definitely
taken an unexpected turn.
[Riz] At least Louis is keeping them
on their toes.
Well, maybe the world won't really change
unless someone shines
a light on these things.
Good to see you and all, but...
don't you have a performance to get to?
You know what, Riz, I really wanted you
to see the play live.
Oh yeah?
You were my first guy friend after all.
[gasp]
Thank you for that.
It's perfectly natural that
herbivores would be worried about this.
That's why,
we have prepared a revolutionary solution.
Okay, talk about the artificial meat.
Got it.
Ibuki,
in the end your greatest sin,
might have been turning me
into a wild buck.
The Black Market...
Is my home.
I was product ID number 4.
[all stunned]
I was a powerless young kid.
Born in a cage.
I was supposed to be sold
in the Black Market as meat.
[crowd gasps]
Is that the truth?
Chairman Ogma purchased me,
and raised me as heir
to The Horns Conglomerate.
He treated me like his own son.
Someone found out about my origins
and threatened my father with it.
That person
is the mayor!
What? Louis, what are you doing?
It's the truth.
The mayor tried to blackmail
an enormous bribe out of my father.
[chuckles nervously]
I have no idea what he's talking about...
Right, father?
[growling]
Um-hmm.
What do you have to say for yourself,
Mr. Mayor?
- Is all this true?
- Fake news.
[Louis] And he didn't stop there.
He extorted money
from the Zoolympics sponsors, too.
This Zoolympic bid is full of dirty money.
Wake up! Don't fall for his lies!
He's a disgrace.
Bringing dishonor to the kings of beasts!
Huh?
[grunting]
[roars]
[crowd screams]
[grunts]
[growls]
Legoshi...
[both grunting]
- [male 5] He's-- He's the devourer!
- [male 6] Someone stop him!
- [male 7] Run away!
- [female] Don't look, Sweetie!
- [male 8] Stay back!
- [male 9] Where are the police?
[strains]
- [male 8] Let's get outta here.
- [male 9] I don't want to die!
[male 5] He might eat us!
[male 4] That's the devourer
from the news!
He's not a devourer!
You're wrong!
He's just Legoshi...
He'd never do something like that!
Wow, I don't think I'd be that brave.
Oh, Legoshi...
Haru...
You're alright.
Yeah. Did you close your eyes?
I was looking at you.
They should be closed when we kiss!
Wanna try again?
Go, Legoshi...
[Haru chuckles softly]
[Yahya] That gray wolf was framed,
he's no devourer.
He's innocent.
I admire his bravery.
He sought justice
in spite of being accused.
He didn't stop until
he captured the actual criminal.
Legoshi...
really well done.
Mr. Yahya...
[applause]
I do apologize, Father.
But I had to.
This is the path I've chosen for myself.
Well sometimes our plans...
don't go the way we want.
Your prosthetic leg
will climb so much higher
than I ever could.
Looks like they really did it.
You're right.
These kids are more than one
single Beastar.
Yeah, they're Beastars.
Right.
[crowd cheering]
[theme song playing]
[voiceover] The drama club
put on their play
shortly after the real life drama
and it was a huge success.
The mayor was arrested
on multiple bribery charges.
And those weren't the only crimes.
Turns out there was blackmail
and intimidation, too.
I'm told that Melon survived,
but I don't know his condition.
As for Louis...
[Juno] So you and I are just done?
I'm sorry.
[Juno] Well, then...
...take care, Louis.
[voice-over] And as for my boy, Legoshi...
I want to be with you,
every day for the rest of my life.
Well...
Is that a proposal?
- Yes it is.
- [groans softly]
A wolf and a rabbit...
That won't be
the easiest of relationships.
But we'll keep going, no matter what.
No, don't bend over!
I can reach up to you!
I'm falling, I'm falling! Hold me!
Uh, Haru!
I see you, wolf!
Let go of her!
[chuckles] It's alright.
We're together! [chuckles]